<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Until It&#39;s Not Fun</title>
    <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Until It&#39;s Not Fun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://untilitsnotfun.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Have a Website</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-07-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-07-08/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about websites After much prep, I finally decided to actually start freelancing this week. I noticed in my hometown that the majority of small businesses there don&amp;rsquo;t have any online presence. They do advertising in the local newspaper, word of mouth, and some use only Facebook. In 2022, there is a whole population of people that these small businesses are missing by not being online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week and Callum</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-07-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-07-01/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about this week With much to do and much to celebrate this past week, this post is going to be a short one and not a wonderful piece of art like all of my previous posts. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much of a muse for a topic to write about this week so instead let&amp;rsquo;s go over the highlights my week:
Tuesday: I got my last clearance for the Peace Corps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorting Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-24/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about sorting This Tuesday, Jacob and I found ourselves with a pile of hundreds of football and baseball cards searching each one on an app to get a rough estimate of their value. We started off by just searching the name of each player one by one but that quickly grew boring and would have taken us months.
Our next workflow was to sort all of them into their individual teams (33 for the NFL and 30 for the MLB) and then look at the most popular in the app and see if we had that player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stocks and Westley</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-17/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies It is Westley J Winks birthday this Sunday (the 19th), and I want to use my column to say how grateful I am to have him as a friend.
(Normally I would send a note privately, but f*** that, the world needs to hear about this guy.)
Westley, you have been my brother for a while now, which means you have seen all the different sides of me, yet you remain my friend; that is a testament to you, and I thank you for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APIs and OBI-WAN KENOBI</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-10/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies OBI-WAN KENOBI 2022
Well, this hits my childhood excitement like I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt in a while!
Disney just released Obi-Wan Kenobi, a spinoff show from the main canon films, it starts basically where the Revenge Of The Sith left off, (Star Wars #3).
It just made me smile when I turned this on, from the same music, the same actors, everything is perfectly in its place from where I wanted it when I finished Revenge Of The Sith all those years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Internet?</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-06-03/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about the internet The internet. We all know it. We all love it.
But what actually is it?
At the most basic physical level, the internet is a bunch of wires connecting all of the computers around the world. That&amp;rsquo;s it! The &amp;ldquo;World Wide Web&amp;rdquo; is literally a web of wires that connect our devices together and allow them to talk to one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proton and Plant Mom</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-27/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies From Jacob: “Hello to our thousands of readers, I apologize but I haven’t had time to really sit down and analyze a film lately, I thought about whipping something together, but decided that isn’t what this is for anyway. Tune in next week I think I’ve got a banger in store!”
The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about Proton I have been using Proton Mail for a few months now instead of using GMail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being a Fan and RSS</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-20/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks about being a fan Not a movie?&amp;hellip; weird.
Jacob talks about being a fan of something.
Go Sports!
Okay, I&amp;rsquo;m testing out a couple of different things here.
The first one is this new app called Otter , where you can talk into it, and it writes down what you&amp;rsquo;re saying. So I can do my columns on the go instead of sitting down and asking Lydia 400 times how to spell something&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown and Barry</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-13/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about Markdown Humans write a lot and most of it is done on computers these days. If someone asked you to write them a letter, where would you start? Most would open up Word or Google Docs. We all know the headaches that these word processors can cause: formatting not doing what you want it to, files getting lost, the person you are sending files to doesn&amp;rsquo;t use the same processor, et cetera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaming With Patrick and The Sisters Brothers</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-05-06/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies The Sisters Brothers (2018) John C. Reilly (Main)
Joaquin Phoenix (Main)
Jake Gyllenhaal (Main)
Man, this is one I&amp;rsquo;m going to watch again soon!
I started watching with my notes in hand, then found myself becoming so pulled into the story I was forgetting to take notes. Finally I gave up trying, and decided to take notes the second time over and fully watch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh and Complibot</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-29/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies Fresh 2022 Daisy Edgar-Jones (Main)
Sebastian Stan (Main)
I can’t tell if this movie is a horror, suspenseful, maybe a romance? But it’s nothing like I’ve seen before! I started watching this with very little insight on the story, so I was on the ride through the whole thing. To me personally, it’s not a movie I’m going to re-watched 5 times like others, but I did enjoy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jammy Jellyfish</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-22/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies Unfortunately, Jacob couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it this week. He should be back with a review next Friday! Until then, you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with me. -Westley
The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about Linux nano content/posts/2022-04-22/index.md
As I am writing this, I am patiently awaiting the release of Jammy Jellyfish &amp;ndash; Ubuntu&amp;rsquo;s 22.04 LTS release. The Ubuntu subreddit and IRC channels are ablaze with newcomers and veterans to Linux alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRC and Pig</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-15/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about IRC /join #untilitsnotfun
/nick dadofapollo
(12:04:08) Westley is now known as dadofapollo
(12:05:16 PM) dadofapollo: IRC (Internet Relay Chat) is a beautiful relic of the internet that helped set the stage for how we communicate on the internet today. IRC was one of the first internet based chat systems. Users can enter different chat rooms called channels and can start communicating with anyone else that is in the same channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Edition: Test Run</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:09:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-11/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies The first movie review was intimidating.
Preface This adventure Westley and I have set out on is purely for enjoyment. So then, why is reviewing a movie intimidating? Not because of the difficulty, but rather, because of the respect I have for this field of &amp;ldquo;Film Making.&amp;rdquo; Resistance will forever be my antagonist, so here&amp;rsquo;s to another battle.
I will probably stick to two types of &amp;ldquo;reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
