<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Until It&#39;s Not Fun</title>
    <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Until It&#39;s Not Fun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jammy Jellyfish</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-22/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies Unfortunately, Jacob couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it this week. He should be back with a review next Friday! Until then, you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with me. -Westley
The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about Linux nano content/posts/2022-04-22/index.md
As I am writing this, I am patiently awaiting the release of Jammy Jellyfish &amp;ndash; Ubuntu&amp;rsquo;s 22.04 LTS release. The Ubuntu subreddit and IRC channels are ablaze with newcomers and veterans to Linux alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRC and Pig</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-15/</guid>
      <description>The Tech Shelf Where Westley talks about IRC /join #untilitsnotfun
/nick dadofapollo
(12:04:08) Westley is now known as dadofapollo
(12:05:16 PM) dadofapollo: IRC (Internet Relay Chat) is a beautiful relic of the internet that helped set the stage for how we communicate on the internet today. IRC was one of the first internet based chat systems. Users can enter different chat rooms called channels and can start communicating with anyone else that is in the same channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Edition: Test Run</title>
      <link>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:09:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://untilitsnotfun.com/posts/2022-04-11/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn and A Coke Where Jacob talks movies The first movie review was intimidating.
Preface This adventure Westley and I have set out on is purely for enjoyment. So then, why is reviewing a movie intimidating? Not because of the difficulty, but rather, because of the respect I have for this field of &amp;ldquo;Film Making.&amp;rdquo; Resistance will forever be my antagonist, so here&amp;rsquo;s to another battle.
I will probably stick to two types of &amp;ldquo;reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
